Workplace Competition Code
职场竞赛守则
I want to poach you
我是想来挖角你
Served as the leader of the Global Communications Group
担任环球传播一组的组长
(Episode 3)
（第3集）
please wait a moment
请等一下
good
好
(Serong Human Resources Office)
（世容人力资源室）
Yes, I am Park Yoon-so
是，我是朴允昭
What?
什么？
(Admission list, Public Relations Office, Business Strategy Headquarters: Park Yoon-soo)
（录取名单 经营策略本部公关室：朴允昭）
right
对
OK, thank you
好，谢谢你
goodbye
再见
Miss Yun Zhao?
允昭小姐？
Feel sorry
抱歉
What did you just say?
你刚才说了什么？
Who called?
是谁打来的电话？
I…
我…
Admitted by Shi Rong
被世容录取了
They have released special recruitment quotas
他们有释出特别招聘名额
That's it
这样啊
(Jae Min)
（才旻）
that…
那个…
Representative Xu, what you just proposed to me...
徐代表，刚才你要向我提议的…
No, nothing
不，没什么
Next time, we'll talk about it later
下次吧，我们以后再说
Listen quickly, I should be calling to congratulate you.
你快听吧，应该是打来恭喜你的
Okay, thank you
好，谢谢
What's wrong?
怎么了？
Shi Rong?
世容吗？
Yeah, I got the call. That's not a big deal.
对，我收到电话了 那又不是什么了不起的事
Come on, of course it's amazing.
拜托，当然很了不起
Hey, am I right?
喂，我说得对吧？
Can not believe it!
真不敢相信！
I just received the call
我才刚收到电话
- The timing is just perfect - Oh my god
-时机也太刚好了 -天啊
Of course we should celebrate this kind of thing
这种事当然要庆祝了
So I want you to promise not to push my face into the cake.
所以我要你保证 不会把我的脸压进蛋糕里
Then I'll pick a really delicious cake
那我就会挑个真正美味的蛋糕
Don't worry about the cake, just come.
别管什么蛋糕了，人来就好
There's no celebration party today
今天不办庆祝派对了
Why?
为什么？
She was clamoring for me to buy a cake just now
她刚才还吵着要我买蛋糕
I don’t know, she’s worried about how to leave her boss now.
我也不知道，她现在又在烦恼 要怎么离开她老板
Please tell her for me that not being nervous is also a virtue.
麻烦替我转告她 不发神经也是种美德
Is there such a saying?
有那种俗语啊？
You are indeed a Chinese major, and your literary attainments are really good.
你果然是中文系的，文学造诣真好
Hey, Xiaomin said, "Not being nervous is also a virtue."
喂，小旻说「不发神经也是种美德」
(Jae Min)
（才旻）
Hey, I'm not crazy, I'm really worried
喂，我没在发神经，我是真的很苦恼
You have never had a good boss, so you cannot empathize with me.
你们没遇过好的上司 所以才无法感同身受
you poor guys
你们这群可怜的家伙
If she doesn't plan to report her death, tell her to reply quickly.
如果她不打算去世容报到 就叫她快点回覆
There are still a bunch of people waiting to be replaced who don’t have to worry about their bosses.
还有一堆不必烦恼 上司问题的人等着递补
I'll close the line first
我先收线了
Did you hear that?
听到了吧？
Is he too heartless sometimes?
他有时候是不是太无情了？
But he's also the smartest among us
但他也是我们之中最聪明的
She also looks the best
长得也最好看
Don't take it too seriously, I just said it casually
别太在意，我只是随口说的
Forget it, you'd better sort out your thoughts.
算了，你还是好好整顿思绪吧
Hello
喂
I've already made up my mind
我心里早就整顿好了
We are just friends now
我们现在只是朋友
Are you talking about our representatives? knew
你说的是我们代表啊？知道了
You crazy woman, really
你这个疯女人，真是的
(Cao Ya Public Relations)
（曹亚公关）
-Representative -What's wrong?
-代表 -怎么了？
Are you going out?
你要外出吗？
Yes, I will get off work directly after finishing the meeting with the client.
对，我待会跟客户开完会就直接下班
If you have nothing to do, just finish packing and go back early.
要是你没什么事 就早点整理完回去吧
-represent! -Yes, what's wrong?
-代表！ -是，怎么了？
-What's up? -that…
-什么事？ -那个…
What's wrong?
怎么了？
Nothing, please walk slowly
没什么，请慢走
Ouch, so boring
唉唷，真没意思
-I am leaving , bye
-我走了 -再见
Why did she leave so early?
她怎么这么早就走了？
(Se Yong, final admission notice for the 2022 special recruitment for people with no qualifications and experience)
（世容，2022年资格不拘 具经验人员特别招聘最终录取通知）
(Hello, I am the person in charge of recruitment at Shirong. I would like to inform you that you have been admitted in 2022...)
（您好，我是世容招聘负责人 在此通知您被录取为2022年…）
(Cao Ya Public Relations)
（曹亚公关）
represent
代表
You're here, Yun Zhao
你来了，允昭
Look at this
你看这个
What do you think this is?
你觉得这是什么？
Chair?
椅子吗？
Yeah?
是吗？
Then I'll make it into a chair
那我就把它做成椅子吧
You are a chair from now on, a chair
你从现在开始就是椅子了，一张椅子
It's so late. Why don't you go home and come to see me instead?
话说这么晚了 你怎么不回家，反而来找我？
I'll tell you after you finish.
等你结束再跟你说吧
What is it?
是什么事？
What's wrong?
怎么了？
What is going on? Say it
到底是什么事？快说
I want to have my own brand
我想拥有自己的品牌
In an agency, I always deal with other people’s brands.
在代理公司总是经手别人名牌的我
That desire began to emerge in my heart
心中开始浮现了那种欲望
Of course I understand that the client's brand is actually equivalent to my...
我当然明白客户的品牌 其实就等同于我的…
please
拜托
Do you think I don't understand that feeling?
你以为我不明白那种心情吗？
I can totally understand
我完全能体会
I have worked in both large companies and agencies.
大企业内部跟代理公司我都待过
I just don’t want my dreams to come to an end in vain
我只是不希望我的梦想 虚无地划下句点
I just have such a good opportunity
又刚好有这么好的机会
congratulations
恭喜你
I'm proud of you, Yun Zhao
我为你感到骄傲，允昭
Sorry, representative
对不起，代表
What's there to be sorry for?
这有什么好对不起的？
Gosh, I sure have a knack for developing talent, right?
天啊，我果然对培养人才 很有一套，对吧？
Are you okay?
你没问题吗？
Alas, just hire new people
唉唷，只要再招聘新人就好
Okay, it's time for us to go
好了，我们该走了
Do you want me to have a drink with you?
要我陪你喝杯酒吗？
Not today, next time
不要今天，下次吧
OK
好的
Are you depressed because Yun Zhao was admitted by Shi Rong ?
你是因为允昭被世容录取 才闷闷不乐吗？
How did you know?
你是怎么知道的？
It's nothing, I just learned about it accidentally
也没什么，只是偶然间得知的
Oh, this is something worth being happy about
唉唷，这是件值得开心的事
But why am I so upset?
但我为什么如此心烦意乱？
I always tell myself not to invest too much emotion , but I always forget it again and again
我总告诫自己不要投注太多感情 却总是一再忘记
Once I develop feelings for them, it won't end well in the end.
我一旦对他们产生感情 最后都没有好下场
Because they will eventually leave for a better way out
因为他们终究会为了 更好的出路而离开
I can't be their final stop
我成为不了他们的终点站
Alas
唉唷
Hey, Dongxun, I seem drunk
喂，东训，我好像喝醉了
Are you so reluctant to give up?
你就那么不舍得吗？
right
对
Not long ago, you clearly asked me to take Park Yun Zhao away.
你不久前明明还叫我把朴允昭带走
Would I feel more relieved if she went to your company ?
她要是去你们公司 我会比较释怀吗？
I was also sad when you left Universal Communications, okay?
你当初离开环球传播时 我也很难过好吗？
But we meet again now
但我们现在又重逢了啊
If we are destined, we will meet again
有缘的话总会再见的
cheers
干杯
Why don't you come back to our company this time?
你不如趁这次回来我们公司吧
You're such a bad boy
你这臭小子真是的
Hey, the position of team leader is too...
喂，组长的职位对我来说太…
Let's get rid of Cao Ya's public relations.
把曹亚公关处理掉吧
The project that Cao Ya Public Relations was originally working on can be taken over by Global Communications
曹亚公关原本在进行的项目 可以交由环球传播接手
Both cosmetics and high-protein bread can continue to advance
化妆品和高蛋白面包都能继续推进
It seems you are not drunk yet
看来你还没喝醉
I'll make you a co-representative
我会让你担任共同代表
Even Shi Yong can't intervene in this kind of thing
就算是世容也无法插手干预这种事
Besides, if we join forces, we will definitely stimulate Shirong hard.
况且我们联手的话 想必会狠狠刺激到世容
Ms. Hanako
花子女士
I was admitted to Shirong
我被世容录取了
No, it’s not beauty, it’s world beauty
不是，不是美容，是世容
It's Shirong
是世容
(Today’s protagonist)
（今日的主角）
-congratulations! -Congratulations, Park Yoon-soo!
-恭喜你！ -恭喜你，朴允昭！
(#job-transfersuccessful, #is actually Shirong)
（#转职成功，#居然是世容）
(#ParkAgent, #新start # enters a big company)
（#朴代理，#新的开始 #进入大企业）
(#UtopiaBoss, # Drink a Cup # is Xiaoen’s treat today)
（#乌托邦老板，#喝一杯 #今天小恩请客）
(#superexcited, #join世grong #celebration party)
（#超兴奋，#加入世容 #庆祝派对）
(#Today’s protagonist, #是Park Agent #ice cream cake)
（#今日的主角，#就是朴代理 #雪糕蛋糕）
-cheers! -bring it on!
-干杯！ -来吧！
congratulations!
恭喜你！
-Park Yun Zhao, congratulations! -Hello!
-朴允昭，恭喜你！ -喂！
Congratulations!
真心恭喜你！
Have fun!
狂欢吧！
Congratulations, Park Yoon-soo!
恭喜你，朴允昭！
-Hey, cheers! -Okay, cheers!
-喂，干杯！ -好，干杯！
Take it!
接招吧！
(#开奖大公司, # Drink, #champagne)
（#跳槽大企业，#喝吧，#香槟）
(#ParkAgent returns, #ParkAgent has a drink)
（#朴代理归来，#朴代理喝一杯）
(#BrilliantSeason, #newstart)
（#灿烂的季节，#新的开始）
(# Welcome to the World #Park Yun Zhao did it, #congratulations)
（#欢迎来到世容 #朴允昭做到了，＃恭喜）
-(Celebrate well!)
-（好好庆祝吧！）
arms together
手臂聚拢
stretch forward
向前伸展
lower your head
把头低下
arm raised
手臂抬高
head up
头抬起来
(Se Yong)
（世容）
look to the front
看向正面
Turn your wrist
转动手腕
then left
接着向左
Reverse direction
反方向
stand up
站起来
push outward
往外推
gather towards body
向身体聚拢
arm circles
手臂转圈
push outward
往外推
stretch to the left
朝左方伸展
stretch to the right
朝右方伸展
stretch down
往下伸展
down
向下
It ends here
到此结束
To all members of the Serong family, I wish you an energetic day.
世容大家庭的各位成员 祝你们度过活力充沛的一天
Those who do public relations these days
这年头做公关的
All lack perseverance
都缺乏毅力
We used to stay up all night drinking
以前我们就算通宵喝酒
I can still arrive at the company on time at 7 a.m. the next day.
隔天还是能准时早上7点到公司
Even if you faint, you will still fall in the company
哪怕会晕倒，也要倒在公司
you are right
你说得没错
When Agent Jin comes, I will definitely tell him
金代理来的时候，我一定会转告他的
Let's go, Agent Liu
走吧，柳代理
OK
好的
Where are you going?
你们要去哪里？
Go to a team leader meeting
去开组长会议
He asked me to personally report to the director of the office. The media promotion strategy is not limited to the plan.
他要我亲自向室长报告 资格不拘计划的媒体宣传策略
Team leader meeting?
组长会议？
This sentence makes my soul feel like it has been ravaged in every possible way
这句话让我的灵魂 仿佛被百般蹂躏了一番
The Bible contains all the truths in the world
《圣经》蕴含着这世间所有的道理
It is recorded inside
里面记载着
"If you seek, you will find. If you knock, the door will open to you."
「只要寻找，便能找到 只要敲门，此门定会为你敞开」
There is nothing impossible in this world
这世上没有做不到的事
Amen
阿们
What's more, those employees who have the strength to enter our world
更何况是那些有实力 能进入我们世容的员工
You shouldn’t make excuses for your lack of ability…
不该为自己能力不足找各种借口…
-Chief Chen -What's wrong?
-陈室长 -怎么了？
I'm sorry to interrupt your precious speech.
很抱歉打断你宝贵的发言
But there is one last item left on the agenda.
不过议程项目还剩最后一项
It’s a public relations press release with no qualifications.
就是资格不拘计划的公关新闻稿
yes
对啊
- Yes - We haven't discussed that yet.
-是 -还没讨论那件事
The representative asked us to exclude "Da Guo Daily"
代表要我们将《大国日报》排除在外
But the consequences of doing so may be unimaginable
但这么做的后果恐怕不堪设想
However, if "Da Guo Daily" is added to the list
不过若把《大国日报》加进名单
-That's tantamount to disobeying the representative's order. -That's it.
-那等于是违抗代表的指令 -就是说啊
She has just been promoted from head office to representative
她才刚从本部长升上代表
So we should pay special attention to her feelings.
所以更要格外顾及她的感受
Yes, you are right
对，你说得没错
So I found the person in charge
所以我把负责人找来了
- You might as well listen to his opinion - Okay
-你不妨听听看他的意见 -好
Just send the press release to the news agency
只要把新闻稿发给通讯社就好
There is no need to send it to Daguo Ilbo and the top ten central comprehensive dailies.
无须发给《大国日报》 及十大中央综合日报
Anyway, whether it’s a TV station or a newspaper
反正无论是电视台或报社
They all receive reports from news agencies
都是接收通讯社的报道
"Daguo Daily" is not the only one who is excluded in this way.
这样被排除在外的 就不只有《大国日报》
It will also be easier for us to cope with
我们在对应上也会比较轻松
sounds good
听起来不错
Just do as you say
就照你说的做吧
As expected of the second group
真不愧是二组
Agent Caimin, do you go to church?
才旻代理，你去教会吗？
No, I am not religious...
没有，我是无宗教…
The so-called faith…
所谓的信仰…
-Chief Chen -huh?
-陈室长 -嗯？
I believe in non-discriminatory employment, regardless of qualifications
我认为无歧视雇用，资格不拘的条件
is a good starting point
是很好的出发点
But why is it our group?
但为何偏偏是我们这组？
Dear Shirong employees
各位亲爱的世容员工
nice to meet you
很高兴见到你们
Given that economies of scale are rapidly…
鉴于经济规模正快速地…
If you are recruiting employees from the public relations department this time,
如果这次招聘的是公关部门员工
Then they should be assigned to the group that plans and executes the project.
那就该把他们指派给 计划并执行这次专案的组别啊
Suddenly putting people into our group will really make it difficult for us to do things.
突然把人安插进我们这组 真的会让我们很难做事
Director Chen
陈室长
- I thought the matter was settled - Yes, it was settled
-我以为这件事已经谈妥了 -对，已经谈妥了
But I never agreed
但我从没同意过
You didn't come to the meeting yourself
是你自己没来参加会议的
I asked to change the meeting time , but you still held the meeting as usual
我有要求变更会议时间 但你还是照样开会啊
If you are unable to attend the meeting due to personal matters , you will have to bear the consequences yourself.
如果是因私事无法参加会议 那后果就要自行承担
This is a company
这里可是公司
Can't you be a little more flexible in what you do?
你做事不能有点变通性吗？
This matter is not that urgent
这件事也没那么急迫
Pool leader
池组长
if that is the case
那样的话
Still have to open it again...
还是要再开一次…
No, no need
不用，不需要
Team Leader Chi is just making trouble unreasonably.
池组长只是在无理取闹罢了
This matter is a foregone conclusion
这件事已成定局
Besides, that employee also came to report today.
况且那名员工今天也来报到了
Pool leader
池组长
You take people away first
你先把人带走
Anyway...
再怎么说…
-Okay, then I'll start... -That's it.
-好吧，那我就先… -就这样吧
So that concludes today’s team leader meeting
那么今天的组长会议就到此结束
-ok -very good
-好的 -很好
Yes, good work
是，辛苦了
Hello, Chi Yinzhen
喂，池银祯
Haven't you seen her resume?
你没看过她的履历表吗？
She works in digital PR
她是做数码公关的
These days, anyone can say that they are in digital public relations.
这年头谁都能说自己是做数码公关的
I can't believe that.
那种话我信不过
So what do you want?
那你想怎样？
Let her join your group!
让她去你们那组啊！
Honestly, I recommend the person who doesn't meet the qualifications.
老实说，力推那个资格不符的人
It's obviously you, because that's how it's topical
明明就是你啊，因为那样才有话题性
Hello!
喂！
Be careful what you say, you know?
你说话注意点，知道吗？
All the newcomers from the past also joined our group.
之前的新人也都丢来我们这组
Do you want our three groups to sit back and wait for death?
是要让我们三组坐以待毙吗？
That's the good thing about being in the public relations room. You can take a break and have a cup of coffee.
待公关室就是这点好 可以自由地偷闲喝杯咖啡
Has Hou Ji come to work?
厚佶来上班了吗？
Damn Kim Ho-gil
该死的金厚佶
Speaking of that brat
说到那个臭小子
you know him now
你知道他现在
Didn't he even reveal which reporters he was drinking with?
都不透露他在跟哪些记者喝酒了吗？
Well managed
管理得不错啊
He will stand out
他会出人头地的
In my opinion, he will only last three years
照我看来，他只会撑三年
He will definitely leave his job within three years and start his own company.
他肯定三年内会离职 然后出去自己开公司
Look, this is a common tactic used by people who love to flatter reporters.
看着吧，这是爱拍记者马屁的人 惯用的手法
This, I'm not interested
这个啊，我不感兴趣
me too
我也是啊
By the way, Team Leader Chi just said something strange.
话说刚才池组长说了些奇怪的话
What words?
什么话？
She said that Team Leader Song strongly recommended Park Yun-soo for this recruitment.
她说这次招聘是宋组长力推朴允昭的
Yeah?
是吗？
Really?
真的吗？
Do you really have no idea?
你真的毫不知情？
Yeah, I really don't know
对，我真的不知道
But how could he push her?
但他要怎么力推她？
Didn't you do a blind test at the beginning?
当初不是做盲测的吗？
anyway
话说回来
Do you know that person who admitted with any qualifications?
你认识那个资格不拘的录取者吗？
Otherwise, why would you be interested?
不然你怎么会感兴趣？
Because that's what I'm responsible for
因为那是我负责的啊
That being said, you're acting a little suspicious.
话虽如此，但你表现得有点可疑
It's time for us to go back
我们该回去了
You know me, right?
你知道我吧？
I have God-given intuition.
我拥有天赐的直觉
I feel it now
我现在感觉到了
Stop drinking coffee and have a beer.
别喝咖啡了，喝杯啤酒吧
Or do you want soju?
还是要烧酒？
All right
好吧
Hello
你好
This is the big conference hall
这里是大会议厅
And here is…
还有这里是…
Agent Jin, this is a newcomer
金代理，这位是新人
-Hello _
-你好
-Okay -I'll go first then
-好 -那我先走了
Please over there
那边请
This is the newcomer who will join us in the future, Ms. Zheng Zhiren.
这位是往后要加入我们的 新人郑芝仁小姐
Say hello
打声招呼吧
Please give me some advice
请多多指教
This is your main work area in the future
这里是你今后主要的工作区域
(Public Relations Group, Team Leader, Cui Yonghao)
（公关一组，组长，崔永皓）
Public Relations Group 2
公关二组
Team leader Song Xuantai
宋宣泰组长
-He... -Super annoying.
-他… -超级讨人厌
No, it's super strong
不是，是超级强势
(Team leader, Song Xuantai)
（组长，宋宣泰）
He's really super strong
他真的超级强势
Also, let’s just pretend we don’t know each other in the company.
还有，我们在公司就假装互不认识吧
Because I hope to rely on myself for everything
因为我希望凡事只靠自己
Can you understand?
你能理解吧？
up to you
随便你
Really
真是的
Then why are you receiving special training now?
那你现在为何要接受特训？
(Public Relations Group Three, Team Leader, Chi Yinzhen)
（公关三组，组长，池银祯）
Public Relations Group 3, also the Digital Public Relations Group
公关三组，也是数码公关组
The team leader is Chi Yinzhen
组长是池银祯
She was the first to become a team leader among those who were publicly recruited at the same time.
她是同期公开招聘的人之中 最早当上组长的
He is also the only deputy chief appointed as the team leader.
也是唯一一个被任命为组长的次长
Team leader Chi, this is Miss Park Yun-jo
池组长，这位是朴允昭小姐
nice to meet you
初次见面，请多多指教
My name is Chi Yinzhen
我叫做池银祯
Then I'll excuse you first.
那我先失陪了
Our group…
我们这组…
Agent Xu
许代理
Yes, Team Leader Chi
是，池组长
Let’s get to know each other
互相认识一下吧
My name is Park Yun-soo, I'm new here
我叫朴允昭，我是新来的
Hello, I'm Xu He, nice to meet you
你好，我是许赫，很高兴认识你
He is a designer personally hired by the digital public relations team to strengthen the design field.
他是数码公关组为了强化设计领域 而亲自录用的设计师
He is in a state of being drained of energy
他正处于精力被榨干的状态
Pool leader
池组长
Have you read the draft I sent you earlier?
你看过我稍早传给你的草稿了吗？
I'll watch that after the meeting.
那个我开完会再看
OK
好的
Agent Xu, you also need to have a meeting together.
许代理，你也要一起开会
But I still have a lot to do…
但我还有很多事要…
Agent Park, this is your seat
朴代理，这是你的位子
Let's go
走吧
"Agent Park"?
「朴代理」？
I haven’t heard anyone call me Agent Park for a long time.
好久没听到别人叫我朴代理了
By the way, the public relations office uses open recruitment
对了，公关室透过公开招聘
The only new person admitted is in the third group
所录取的唯一一个新人就在三组
Otherwise, why would I come to work in a place like this?
否则我为什么要来这种地方上班？
No work-life balance , even the salary sucks
工作与生活达不到平衡 就连薪水也糟透了
Then just leave
那你就走人啊
Yes, that's what I meant, so I'm going to stop doing it from today on
对，我正有此意 所以我打算从今天开始就不做了
Could it be that you are the one who has no qualifications...
你该不会就是那个资格不拘…
Unexpectedly, we met again
没想到又见面了
It seems we are really destined
看来我们还真有缘
what is this? Am I dreaming?
这算什么？我在发梦吗？
I can hear everything
我都听得见
(Se Yong)
（世容）
(Announcement: Personnel Appointment Notice)
（公告：人事任命通知）
Do you know about this?
你知道这件事吗？
Yes, Director Chen
是，陈室长
Yes, okay, I'll go there now
是，好的，我现在就过去
Team Leader Cui!
崔组长！
(Personnel Appointment Announcement Koo Yi-jung, Chief Public Relations Officer)
（人事任命公告 具伊贞，首席公关长）
She was hired to be the chief public relations officer and executive director?
她被挖来当首席公关长兼专务理事？
Se Yong's chief public relations officer?
世容的首席公关长？
It's really unheard of
真是前所未闻
Then isn't she our direct supervisor?
那她不就是我们的直属上司吗？
That's why everyone is in a mess now
所以大家现在才乱成一团啊
The chief public relations officer is the immediate boss of the public relations office
首席公关长是公关室的顶头上司
But the PR office knew nothing about this personnel appointment?
但公关室却对这次的 人事任命一无所知？
Will Director Chen be fired?
那陈室长会被开除吗？
It's hard to say. The life span of a high-level boss can be described as life and death.
这很难说，高阶上司的生存期 可谓是朝生暮死
Why didn't you say a word?
你怎么一句话都不说？
(Koo Yi-jung, Chief Public Relations Officer)
（具伊贞，首席公关长）
What's wrong?
怎么了？
Is it someone you know?
是你认识的人吗？
Don't you know this person?
你不认识这位吗？
Yes, Agent Jae Min
是的，才旻代理
I don't know who she is
我不知道她是谁
“Gizada”
“吉萨达”
This name is so funny
这个名字真好笑
So who is she?
所以她到底是谁？
It's really her
果真是她
Cable News Network has also published several interviews with her.
有线电视新闻网也曾多次刊登 她的采访报道
She is a public relations expert
她是位公关专家
Is she coming to our company?
是她要来我们公司吗？
hello
你们好
Thanks
谢谢
Director Gu
具理事
Um
嗯
The company should make an announcement now
公司现在应该发出公告了
But it's time to get off work now
但现在是下班时间
This is the representative's instruction
这是代表的指示
You will be staying in the same hotel as the representative for the time being
你暂时会跟代表住在同一间酒店
You do not mind right?
你不介意吧？
I'm very mind
我很介意
But what else can be done?
但还能怎么办？
I can only find a place to live as soon as possible
我只能尽快找地方住了
Right?
对吧？
Director of Strategy Office, Director of Human Resources Office , Director of Secretarial Office
战略办公室主任、人力资源办公室主任 、秘书室主任
Only these few people know about this
只有这几个人知道这件事
Of course, this is what Representative Lin meant
当然，这是林代表的意思
No one knows what she is thinking
没人知道她到底在想些什么
They actually created a new position of chief public relations officer and brought people back.
居然新设首席公关长的职位 还将人带回来
She must have drunk too much foreign ink , so she doesn’t understand how things work in Korea.
想必她是洋墨水喝多了 所以根本不了解韩国的运作情况
I'm worried she'll do other ridiculous things
我担心她还会做出其他荒谬的举动
This was the first thing she prepared after taking office as the representative director.
这是她上任代表理事后 所筹备的第一件事
I think she should have her own plan
我想她应该自有打算
Go and inquire more carefully
再去仔细打听一下
Let’s see what kind of work she does mainly
看她主要都做了哪些工作
Yes, I understand
是，我知道了
Since she became a representative
自从她当上代表后
The position of the head of the Strategy Headquarters is now vacant.
策略本部长的位子就空了下来
If there is a suitable candidate, please introduce it to me.
若有适合的人选就介绍给我吧
People from our camp?
我们阵营的人吗？
suitable person
适合的人
Yes, I understand
是，我知道了
(Vice President, Zheng Qiurong)
（副社长，郑求荣）
It's time to get off work
该下班了
Let me see…
我看看…
OK, let's go
好，走吧
what time is it now?
现在几点了？
It turns out it’s already so late
原来已经这么晚了
Hey, did you hear that? There's a new chief public relations officer in the public relations office.
喂，你听说了吗？ 公关室有个新来的首席公关长
Chief public relations officer?
首席公关长？
-What's that for? -I don't know either
-那是做什么的？ -我也不知道
It seems there was an announcement just now
刚才好像有发出公告
Yeah?
是吗？
You drink coffee, right?
你喝咖啡的吧？
Thank you
谢谢你
You seem to get off work very late
你好像都很晚才下班
How can I help?
有什么需要我帮忙的吗？
(Se Yong, login)
（世容，登入）
I heard that after the personnel appointment announcement was released, there was a lot of discussion throughout the company.
听说人事任命公告发布后 公司上下就议论纷纷的
But I don't have permission to log into the company intranet yet
但我还没有权限登入公司内联网
(Welcome to the World Internet)
（欢迎来到世容内联网）
(Personnel Appointment Announcement Koo Yi-jung, Chief Public Relations Officer)
（人事任命公告 具伊贞，首席公关长）
"Gizada"?
“吉萨达”？
I'm going to work
我要工作了
- Goo Yi Jung - What?
-具伊贞 -什么？
She is that Goo Yi Jung, right?
她就是那位具伊贞，对吧？
-Don’t you know Goo Yi Jung? -I really don't know who she is
-你不认识具伊贞吗？ -我真的不知道她是谁
Not really possible today
今天真的不行
- Just promise me this time! What's wrong? -ah
-你就答应我这一次吧！怎么了？ -啊
Brother Zhejun, wait, this is very important.
哲俊哥，等等，这很重要
Is the new chief public relations officer the same Goo Yi-jung?
新来的首席公关长 就是那位具伊贞吗？
Yes, she is the public relations expert who appeared in that internationally renowned magazine this time.
没错，她就是这次登上 那本国际著名杂志的公关专家
That's Goo Yi Jung
就是那个具伊贞
-Yoo Jae-min! -Oh my god
-柳才旻！ -天啊
- Wait, wait a minute - Please, just once
-等等，等一下 -拜托，一次就好
I beg you, I beg you
我拜托你，算我求你了
-Jaemin! -no!
-才旻！ -不行！
(Serong hopes to strengthen its public relations capabilities by introducing new senior executives)
（世容期盼藉由引进新任高层 来加强公关能力）
Hey, please confirm
喂，你确认看看
OK, thanks
好的，谢谢
A publication published by a little-known company like this
像这种名不见经传的小公司 所发行的刊物
Besides company employees, who else would read it?
除了公司员工，还有谁会看啊？
boss
老板
Do you know this person?
你认识这位吗？
who is she?
她是谁？
She left Zter not long ago
她不久前刚离开兹特尔
Switched to public relations career for American start-up companies
转而投身美国新创公司的公关事业
what are you saying?
你在说什么？
I'm not going to spend my whole life making company publications.
我不会一辈子都在制作公司刊物
I want to be like her in the future
我将来也想成为像她那样的人
She should have also produced company publications in the beginning.
她一开始应该也制作过公司刊物
Have you confirmed it?
你确认完了吗？
Yes, let me confirm
是，我确认一下
Really
真是的
Alas
唉唷
(Coco Promotional Event, we are having a meeting)
（可可宣传活动，我们正在开会）
(Xiao Zhao, exhausted, dreamed that Duke Zhou was gone)
（小昭，精疲力尽，梦周公去了）
(Li Sejiang, happy birthday)
（李瑟蒋，生日快乐）
(Tonight you and I will become one)
（今夜你和我将合而为一）
-(Keep on partying...)
-（继续狂欢吧…）
- (Drink a drink...)
-（喝一杯…）
(We're going to drink until we can't drink anymore. Let's have another drink)
（我们要喝到不能喝为止 再干一杯吧）
OK, come together
好，一起来
- (Drink a drink)
-（喝一杯）
The wine is going down my throat
酒要入喉了
-Keep drinking!
-继续喝！
very good!
非常好！
-good
-好
Everyone, sit down, sit down...
大家坐下，坐下来…
Hello! Don't sit down. What are you doing sitting down? What's wrong?
喂！不要坐，坐下来做什么？ 怎么了？
Oh my god, my daughter is back.
天啊，我女儿回来了
-my daughter -she's so beautiful
-我的女儿 -长得真漂亮
Welcome back!
欢迎回来！
-Saeyong!
-世容！
-What's wrong?
-怎么了？
-pocket money!
-零用钱！
Continue to the third stall!
续第三摊！
-good! Go to the third stall! -good!
-好！去续第三摊吧！ -好！
Come on, keep on partying!
来吧，继续狂欢！
Awesome…
真棒…
marvelous
太棒了
Come, have another drink
来，再干一杯
It tastes so good, it just gets better.
真好喝，味道变得更好了
Where are you?
你在哪里？
(Kaiming)
（凯明）
I'm going to spend the night at a friend's house
我要在朋友家过夜
- (Let's have a drink)
-（干一杯吧）
Have you been back?
你回来过了？
So annoying
烦死了
The guard guy kept running up , and even the police came
警卫大叔一直跑上来 就连警察也来过了
By the way, when you pay me, you will help me buy a pair of brand-name sneakers.
对了，等你出粮 要帮我买双名牌运动鞋
Get away
滚开
(Se Yong)
（世容）
Ouch, I'm almost exhausted
唉唷，快累死了
Hello
你好
-Hi -Hmm
-嗨 -嗯
Why don't you give me some hints?
你好歹也给点暗示吧
unacceptable
太过分了
That's a special instruction from the representative. I have to keep it a secret.
那是代表特别指示的，我要保密才行
but
不过
I really can't understand
我真的无法理解
Just add a rank above the director of the public relations office
只是在公关室室长之上添个职级
Is it necessary to make it look like an espionage war?
有必要搞得像谍报战一样吗？
-I don’t know about that either. -Young Master
-那个我也不知道 -少来了
I am not kidding
我是说真的
Maybe the head of the strategy room will know
也许策略室室长会知道
He doesn't answer the phone at all
他根本不听电话
Chief Kim called me just now
刚才金本部长打给我
He said that the vice president asked him to find someone who could be the head of the Strategy Headquarters.
他说副社长要他去找 能胜任策略本部长的人选
What?
什么？
In other words, if even the head of the Strategy Headquarters is from the vice president's side...
也就是说万一连策略本部长 都是副社长那边的人…
That means...
那代表就…
She will become in name only
她就会变得有名无实
You should know how much the vice president loves the media, right?
你应该知道副社长有多热爱媒体吧？
He still reads the newspaper every day
他到现在还是每天看报纸
You need to prepare a plan for this time that the qualifications are not restricted.
你要筹备好这次的资格不拘计划
Try to be as high-profile as possible
尽量高调一点
Cai Min
才旻
yes
是
this
这个
(Publicity strategy for the plan of independent qualifications, Public Relations Office, Park Yoon-so)
（资格不拘计划的宣传策略 公关室，朴允昭）
Help me think of some more powerful moves to strengthen them.
帮我想些更厉害的招数加强一下
(Internal company channel interview)
（公司内部频道采访）
(Newspaper interview, magazine interview, TV interview)
（报纸采访，杂志采访，电视采访）
(Publicity strategy for the plan of independent qualifications, Public Relations Office, Park Yoon-so)
（资格不拘计划的宣传策略 公关室，朴允昭）
That, Team Leader Chi
那个，池组长
-What's up? -What should I do next?
-什么事？ -我之后该做些什么？
Go investigate the Serong Public Relations Office
去调查一下世容公关室
-Business results to date -Yes
-至今为止的业务成果 -是
Then I'll confirm the information first and then contact you.
那我先确认一下资料再跟你联系
goodbye
再见
(Hummer achieved sales of KRW 1 trillion with self-developed products )
（悍马以自家开发产品 达成一兆韩圜销售额）
(March 2022, news clipping)
（2022年3月，新闻剪报）
Hey, look outside
喂，你看外面
- it's a garden - and there's a garden
-是花园 -还有花园
Yes, we have a garden
对，我们有花园
-Hello -you are here
-你好 -你来了啊
right
对
No one will use that bar
没有人会用那个吧台
That's Representative Xu's office
那里是徐代表的办公室
There is the conference room
那里则是会议室
That's my office
那间是我的办公室
Why would you buy something like this?
怎么还买这种东西过来？
Representative, Global Communication is beautiful
代表，环球传播很漂亮
Beautiful, right?
很美吧？
Because Dongxun majored in design
因为东训是读设计的
He decorated this place himself
这里都是他亲自装潢的
He's really talented
他还真有才华
He will come over later, let's have dinner together
他等一下会过来，一起吃晚餐吧
Of course I am honored to have dinner with these two representatives.
我当然很荣幸能跟两位代表一起吃饭
How are you doing in this world?
你在世容过得如何？
It's great. Everyone is very kind to me.
很好啊，大家都对我很亲切
I have something I want to tell you face to face
我有些事想当面跟你说
What's up?
什么事？
Hello
你好
Yun Zhao, Shi Rong wants to get your plan
允昭，世容想取得你的计划书
I only found out later
我也是后来才知道的
Shirong
世容
Intend to adopt your plan
打算采用你的计划书
(Sildis’ online and offline event proposals, Cao Ya Public Relations)
（西尔迪斯线上及线下活动提案 曹亚公关）
I've always wanted to tell you
我一直很想告诉你
But I can't find the right time
但找不到适合的时机
represent
代表
I wrote this proposal as Cao Ya's public relations staff .
我是以曹亚公关职员的身分 来撰写这份计划书的
Since you're working here now, it's up to you to take over.
既然你现时在这里工作 理当由你来接手才对
Shi Rong still doesn’t know that I’m working here.
世容那边还不知道我来这里工作
They want to spread the word around the world and it’s up to them.
他们要环球传播自己看着办
I see
原来如此
I…
我…
Can you leave first?
可以先离开吧？
Let’s have dinner next time, Representative
晚餐下次再吃吧，代表
no problem
好，没问题
Senior, why did Miss Yun Zhao just leave?
前辈，允昭小姐怎么直接走了？
I told her about the plan
我跟她说了计划书的事
I think it's up to me to say
我认为应该由我来说才对
sorry
对不起
what are you saying?
你在说什么？
That was an offer that was impossible to refuse.
那是个令人无法拒绝的提案
No, it should be said to be an order
不对，应该说是命令
So don't take it too seriously
所以你别太在意了
But I still feel very guilty for her
但我还是对她感到很愧疚
That's true
那倒也是
I really feel sorry for her, that's right
确实是挺对不起她的，没错
(Eligibility is not subject to program promotion strategy)
（资格不拘计划宣传策略）
(Public Relations Office, Park Yun-soo)
（公关室，朴允昭）
no
不是啊
To drain her of all her worth
要榨干她的价值
Just having to digest these schedules is enough to leave her with no time to do other work.
光是要消化这些行程 就足以让她无暇做其他工作了
What other job does she have?
她有什么其他工作？
Hey, this is her job
喂，这就是她的工作
Become an Advocate for the Eligibility-Free Program
成为资格不拘计划的代言人
That's why she was admitted
那就是她被录取的理由
But it’s time to stop.
但也该适可而止吧
I will reschedule
我会重新安排的
Agent Liu
柳代理
Hello! Agent Liu!
喂！柳代理！
Yes, team leader
是，组长
How is the global communications plan going?
环球传播的计划书进行得如何？
-Sildis' project -The other party has not yet given a definite reply.
-西尔迪斯的项目 -对方还没确切回覆
what are they going to do
他们打算怎么做
Why? Have you made it clear to them?
为什么？你有跟他们说清楚吗？
Can't you even convey the company's intentions well?
你连转达公司的意思都做不好吗？
It seems like you're just relaying it like a megaphone again
看来你又只像个传声筒一样转述
Didn't understand the meaning at all
完全没有理解其中的意思
Do you really have a way to manage those agencies well?
你这样真的有办法 好好管理那些代理公司吗？
Go back and explain it clearly to them.
再去跟他们好好说清楚
Do you understand what I'm trying to say?
你理解我想表达的意思吗？
Please use your brain, Jaemin.
拜托用点脑吧，才旻
so what you mean is
所以你的意思是
We adopt the plan from Cao Ya Public Relations
我们采用曹亚公关的计划书
Completely out of necessity
完全是迫于无奈
Because all team leaders were not hired through open recruitment.
因为并非经由公开招聘 而入职的全组长
I have the support of Minister Kim behind me.
背后有金本部长撑腰
Therefore, Global Media should arbitrarily steal other people’s plans.
所以看环球传播要蛮横地 抢走别人的计划书
Or you have to spend your own money to buy it.
还是要自己花钱买下来都行
Is this what you want to convey?
这就是你想传达的意思吧？
Yes, that's right
对，没错
-That's what it means . -Okay, then I get it.
-就是那个意思 -好，那我知道了
That madman
那个疯子
I seem to see myself when I was young
我仿佛看到了年轻时的我
Go crazy and deny your relatives
疯起来六亲不认
Team Leader Cui!
崔组长！
I shouted too loudly
我叫太大声了
this
这个
smokes
抽烟
I don't want to smoke
我又不想抽烟
Just now, Team Leader Song
刚才宋组长
Did you run away in despair?
落荒而逃了吧？
He must feel so embarrassed
他一定觉得很丢脸
He certainly never thought that those words he said would turn Yijun against him.
他肯定没想过会被 自己说的那些话反将一军
Alas, Agent Liu
唉唷，柳代理
I appreciate your madness very much
我非常赞赏你的疯狂
If it were me, I would be fired immediately
如果换作是我，肯定立刻被开除
It seems that the trump card is still the trump card even if it goes astray.
看来王牌就算走偏了也还是王牌
This society is really unfair, right?
这个社会还真是不公平，对吧？
i was chosen
我被选中了
What do you want from me?
找我做什么？
Mad Ace
疯子王牌
It's up to you to decide
这给你看着办
-why me? -This is your job.
-为什么是我？ -这本来就是你的工作啊
- But not anymore - Are you kidding me?
-但现在不是了 -你在开玩笑吗？
Didn’t you say you must be promoted this time?
你不是说你这次一定要升迁吗？
Without this, you're totally screwed
要是没有这个，你就彻底完蛋了
correct
对了
i am being punished
我正在受罚
As long as you know
你知道就好
Let’s talk about this plan
话说这个计划书
Was it the Cao Ya public relations employee with no qualifications who did it?
是那个资格不拘的 曹亚公关员工做的吧？
The representative of Cao Ya PR worked in Serong before.
曹亚公关的代表以前在世容工作过啊
When we were pitching proposals, I told her that the finalist was already determined to be Global Communications
之前比稿提案时，我告诉她 入选者已经内定是环球传播
Ask her not to have high expectations
要她别抱太大的期望
But it turned out like this
但结果却变成这样
-Why is it always so bad? -because we made a mess
-为什么总是如此不顺？ -因为我们把事情搞得一团糟
Do you know the posts about Shi Yong in the Nonsense Forum ?
你知道胡说八道讨论区里 有关世容的贴文
Why is it always less than other companies?
为何总是比其他公司少吗？
-Because everyone gave up? -no
-因为大家都放弃了？ -不是
It’s because what we do lets others know
是因为我们做的事让别人知道
I really couldn’t hold my head up, so everyone couldn’t hold back from writing.
真的会抬不起头，大家才忍住不写的
I totally understand
我完全能理解
Don't call her "regardless of qualifications" anymore
以后别再叫她「资格不拘」了
I want to call her Agent Park Yoon-so
要称呼她为朴允昭代理
What?
什么？
Yes, that’s right, I like her. I’ve had a crush on her for a long time. Are you satisfied?
对，没错，我喜欢她 我暗恋她很久了，满意了吗？
What?
什么？
So is the global communications team responsible for Sirdis' project ?
那么西尔迪斯的项目 是由环球传播一组负责吗？
Yes
是的
I heard that it is currently supervised by Representative Seo Donghun personally.
听说目前是由徐东训代表亲自监督
Really?
真的吗？
Who will be responsible for those three groups?
那三组要由谁来负责？
I'm willing to give it a try
我愿意试试看
you are not qualified yet
你还不够资格
It seems that I can only take responsibility personally.
看来只能由我亲自负责了
That’s why I ask that qualifications be taken into consideration when replacing people.
所以我才会要求补人时要看重资历
Pool leader
池组长
Change to next project
换下一个项目
This plan…
这个计划书…
I said I'm responsible
我说了由我负责
Any questions?
有什么问题吗？
No
没有
nothing
没什么
(Se Yong)
（世容）
Pool leader
池组长
What's up?
什么事？
About the Sildis Plan that Global Communications is responsible for
关于环球传播所负责的 西尔迪斯计划书
That's actually the plan I made
那其实是我做的计划书
Then what?
然后呢？
Please leave the Sildis plan to me.
请把西尔迪斯计划书交给我负责
Please let me work on this project with Global Communications
请让我跟环球传播一起进行这个项目
I am confident that I will do better than anyone else
我有信心会做得比谁都好
no
不行
Please familiarize yourself with your current job content first
请你先熟悉目前的工作内容
-Team Leader Chi -You can get off work now
-池组长 -你可以下班了
Pool leader
池组长
It only takes a few days to become familiar with the work content
熟悉工作内容只需要几天
I've been doing digital PR in the past so I'm familiar with
我过去一直从事数码公关 所以我很熟悉
-That plan... -I said I'm in charge!
-那个计划书… -我说了由我负责！
This is an important project and I must be responsible for it
这是个重要的项目，必须由我负责
How many times do you want me to speak?
要我讲多少次啊？
You said it only takes a few days to familiarize yourself with the work content?
你说熟悉工作内容只需要几天？
You said you've been doing it for a long time?
你说你做了很久？
Where is it done?
在哪里做的？
Are they working for agencies whose names I've never even heard of ?
是在那些连名字都没听过的 代理公司吗？
Just because people like you are neither powerful nor trustworthy
就因为你们这种人 既没实力又不值得信赖
We will distribute your plan to the world, right?
我们才会把你们的计划书 给环球传播，不是吗？
You should be ashamed
你该感到羞愧才是
How dare you do it casually...
居然敢随便…
I have eight years of relevant work experience, team leader
我拥有八年的相关工作经历，组长
No one knows what you did in other companies during those eight years.
没人知道那八年里 你在外面的公司做了些什么
Even if you have eight years of experience, you may not be as good as Se Rong, a newcomer.
就算拥有八年资历 你可能还比不上世容的新人
As far as I'm concerned, there's no difference between you and that newcomer Ji Hyo.
就我看来，你跟那个新人智孝 根本没什么区别
Do you understand your position now?
你现在明白自己的位置了吗？
I still don't agree that you are capable enough to join Serong's public relations team.
我还不认同你有足够的能力 可以进入世容公关组
Agent Park
朴代理
Don’t cry in front of me again
以后不准在我面前哭
Never negotiate with tears
绝对不要用眼泪来协商
That's the worst way
那是最糟的方式
(The characters, events, groups, organizational backgrounds, etc. in this drama are purely fictitious. We hereby inform you)
（本剧之人物、事件、团体、组织 背景等纯属虚构，特此告知）
Subtitle translation: Wu Jingyi
字幕翻译：伍静怡